dyslexiaida.org 2017-02-21

# Donor Privacy Policy

              INTERNATIONAL DYSLEXIA ASSOCIATION, INC.
                            Donor Privacy Policy
The International Dyslexia Association, Inc. (IDA) is committed to respecting the privacy
of our donors. We have developed this privacy policy to ensure our donors that donor
information will not be shared with any third party.
Awareness. IDA provides this Donor Privacy Policy to make you aware of our privacy
policy, and to inform you of the way your information is used. We also provide you with
the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list, if you desire to do so.
Information Collected. Here are the types of donor information that we collect and
maintain:
    contact information: name, organization, complete address, phone number, email
      address;
    payment information: credit card number and expiration date, and billing information;
    shipping information: name, organization, complete address;
How Information is Used. IDA uses your information to understand your needs and
provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you
complete a transaction and to communicate back to you. Credit card numbers are used
only for donation or payment processing and are not retained for other purposes. We use
the comments you offer to provide you with information requested, and we take seriously
each recommendation as to how we might improve communication.
No Sharing of Personal Information. IDA will not sell, rent, or lease your personal
information to other organizations. We assure you that the identity of all our donors will
be kept confidential. Use of donor information will be limited to the internal purposes of
IDA and only to further the activities and purposes of IDA.
Removing Your Name From Our Mailing List. It is our desire to not send unwanted
mail to our donors. Please contact us if you wish to be removed from our mailing list.
Contacting Us. If you have comments or questions about our donor privacy policy,
please contact us at (410) 296-0232.
